M. Gardner Clark Papers /4309
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
M. Gardner Clark Papers
1947-1993
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Clark, M. Gardner
/4309
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
8491368
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Clark, M. Gardner (Mills Gardner), 1917-
8491368
- Foreign Workers - in EUROPE (Box 1, Folder 1)
- SWUnN - TRAINING and YOUTH (Box 1, Folder 2)
- SWUnN - INTERVIEWS (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SWI-BIBLIO and NAMES (Box 1, Folder 4)
- FW - BERNE Interviews (Box 1, Folder 5)
- FW - OFIAMT - B16A (Box 1, Folder 6)
- FW - FREMDENPOLIZEI (Box 1, Folder 7)
- FW - Sch. Arbeitgeber Zeitieng (Box 1, Folder 8)
- FW - Revue syndicale suisse (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Foreign Workers (Box 1, Folder 10)
- SWI - MISC. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- SUMMARY ARTICLE (Box 1, Folder 12)
- SOC Part One - MACRO DATA (Box 1, Folder 13)
- SOC Part II - Results in Perspective (Box 1, Folder 14)
- SOC Part III - Explain Part I (Box 1, Folder 15)
- SOC Pt. V - EUR (Box 1, Folder 16)
- SOC Ch. VI Analytical MODEL (Box 1, Folder 17)
- SOC Ch. VII Exo Character (Box 1, Folder 18)
- SOC Pt. VI - Effects Exo (Box 1, Folder 19)
- SOC Pt. VII - Effect Mansholt (Box 1, Folder 20)
- SOC - MISC. (Box 1, Folder 21)
- ITALY - MISC. (Box 1, Folder 22)
- I - INTRO and MODELS (Box 1, Folder 23)
- II - NATIONAL PATTERNS - DATA (Box 1, Folder 24)
- III - QUAL. ASPECTS of EXO (Box 1, Folder 25)
- POP DATA - MISC. (Box 1, Folder 26)
- IV - REGIONAL CONTRASTS - DATA (Box 1, Folder 27)
- B - NATURAL GROWTH (Box 1, Folder 28)
- C - UnN and LF PARTCIP. (Box 1, Folder 29)
- A - RUR EXO-URBANIZATION (Box 1, Folder 30)
- D - AGR. EXO (Box 1, Folder 31)
- V - AGR and INTERNAL MIG (Box 2, Folder 1)
- VI - AGR and EXTERNAL MIG (Box 2, Folder 2)
- History to Mus (Box 2, Folder 3)
- MUS (Box 2, Folder 4)
- POST to 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- CAP-1, 1958-1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- CAP-2, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- MISC. - Future, Conclusions (Box 2, Folder 8)
- CENSIS (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Italian Correspondence thru 1954 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Italian Correspondence from 1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- PMI - ANALYSIS - Methodology (Box 2, Folder 12)
- PMI - BIBLIO and NAMES (Box 2, Folder 13)
- PMI - JOB ROLE (Box 2, Folder 14)
- PMI - BIG FIRMS (Box 2, Folder 15)
- PMI - Causal Factors (Box 2, Folder 16)
- PMI - STATE Enterprise (Box 2, Folder 17)
- PMI - INDUSTRIES (Box 2, Folder 18)
- PMI - CRAFTS (Box 2, Folder 19)
- PMI - Part time PT (Box 2, Folder 20)
- PMI - Underground (Box 2, Folder 21)
- PMI - DOMESTIC (Box 2, Folder 22)
- PMI - TOURISM (Box 2, Folder 23)
- PMI - AGRICULTURE (Box 2, Folder 24)
- PMI - TRADE (Box 2, Folder 25)
- PMI - NORTH (Box 3, Folder 1)
- PMI - CENTER (Box 3, Folder 2)
- PMI - SOUTH (Box 3, Folder 3)
- PMI - USA (Box 3, Folder 4)
- PMI - MISC. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- ITALY - BIBLIOGRAPHY (Box 3, Folder 6)
- MOUNTAIN - GEOGR-ZONE EXO (Box 3, Folder 7)
- ITALY - REGIONAL SYSTEM (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ITALY - URB Problems (Box 3, Folder 9)
- ITALY - MEZZOGIORNO Misc. (Box 3, Folder 10)
- ITALY - STATE HOLDINGS - MISC. (Box 3, Folder 11)
- ITALY - AGRICULTURE (Box 3, Folder 12)
- ITALY - TOURISM (Box 3, Folder 13)
- ITALY - IRI (Box 3, Folder 14)
- ITALY - POP, MIGRATION, EMPLOYMENT (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Summary of Manuscript (Box 3, Folder 16)
- RUR - NAMES & Addresses (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Economics (Box 3, Folder 18)
- ENGLISH Language in USA (Box 3, Folder 19)
- FOREIGN WORKERS (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Fiscal Affairs (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Future Research (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Art GOLDSMITH (Box 3, Folder 23)
- INDUSTRIAL ORGANIZATION AND CONTROL (Box 3, Folder 24)
- International Economic Relations (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Iron and Steel (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Labor Economics (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Military and Naval Affairs (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Money & Banking (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Harold OAKLANDER (Box 4, Folder 4)
- POLITICAL ECONOMY (Box 4, Folder 5)
- POLITICS (Box 4, Folder 6)
- POPULATION (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Psychology (Box 4, Folder 8)
- RETIREMENT and PENSIONS (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Science (Box 4, Folder 10)
- SOCIAL SECURITY (Box 4, Folder 11)
- SOCIOLOGY (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Technology (Box 4, Folder 13)
- WELFARE (Box 4, Folder 14)
- WOMEN (Box 4, Folder 15)
- AFGHANISTAN (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Africa - Misc. (Box 4, Folder 17)
- ASIA - MISC. (Box 4, Folder 18)
- China (Box 4, Folder 19)
- East Europe (Box 4, Folder 20)
- EUROPE - MISC. (Box 4, Folder 21)
- France (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Germany (Box 4, Folder 23)
- IRAN (Box 4, Folder 24)
- ITALY thru 1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Japan (Box 4, Folder 26)
- LATIN AMERICA - MISC. (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Mexico (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Middle East (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Poland (Box 4, Folder 30)
- RUSSIA (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Spain (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Turkey (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Yugoslavia (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Foreign Workers (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Future Research (Box 4, Folder 36)
- ILR 140 LECTURES (Box 4, Folder 37)
- SWITZERLAND (Box 5, Folder 1)
- ILR Course on DEVELOPMENT OF ECONOMIC INSTITUTIONS (Box 5, Folder 2)
- A-B (Box 5, Folder 3)
- C-D (Box 5, Folder 4)
- E-F (Box 5, Folder 5)
- G-H (Box 5, Folder 6)
- I-J (Box 5, Folder 7)
- K-L (Box 5, Folder 8)
- M-N-O (Box 5, Folder 9)
- P-Q-R (Box 5, Folder 10)
- S-T (Box 5, Folder 11)
- U-V-W (Box 5, Folder 12)
- X-Y-Z (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Misc. (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Harvard Honor's Thesis (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Articles - M.G. Clark (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Personal Clippings (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Soviet Trip - Diary (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Soviet Visitation, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- STUDENT RECOMMENDATIONS (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Talks (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Dean Robert B. McKersie (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Charles M. Rehmus Dean (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Dean Robert Doherty (Box 5, Folder 24)
- ILR History (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Cornell Upheaval, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Dean M. P. Catherwood, 1947-1956 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Dean M. P. Catherwood, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- ILR Dean - (John W. McConnell) (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Dean Ed. LAWLER (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Misc. Correspondence, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- MISC. CORRESPONDENCE SINCE 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- WAGE STRUCTURES IN THE STEEL INDUSTRY (Box 6, Folder 7)
- SCHUMPETER - Econ THEORY (Box 6, Folder 8)
- REPORT ON NOWA HUTA, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- MEXICO'S POPULATION PROBLEM (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Reprints (Box 6, Folder 11)
- AGRICULTURAL SOCIAL SECURITY AND RURAL EXODUS IN ITALY (Box 6, Folder 12)
- JAPAN INSTITUTE OF FOREIGN AFFAIRS (Box 6, Folder 13)
- REPRINTS: ITALY (Box 6, Folder 14)
- SOVIET AGRICULTURE (Box 6, Folder 15)
- THE SOVIET STEEL INDUSTRY (Box 6, Folder 16)
- REPRINTS: SWITZERLAND (Box 6, Folder 17)
- CHINESE STEEL INDUSTRY (Box 6, Folder 18)